learn2type.com 2015-04-07

# Typing Test and Free Learn to Type Tutor Online - Privacy Statement

**Copyrighted Typing Test Technology**

Content and materials on this website are Copyright ©1999-2015 Learn2Type.com, Inc. 

Access to this website and content is provided at no charge, and with no   
guarantees. While this content has been made available to assist you in   
mastering touch typing, no guarantee is made that it will improve your typing. 

Learn2Type.com, Inc. is not liable for any damages, consequential or inconsequential, from   
the ability or disability of using this website. Use these materials at your own risk. 

Usage of this website constitutes acknowledgment of these disclaimers and terms. 

If you have any questions or concerns, please [contact us with the online feedback form](http://www.learn2type.com/Feedback). 

* * *

**Privacy And Security**

Learn2Type.com, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Learn2Type.com. Your IP address is used to help identify you and tailor your typing lessons and to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your session. We use cookies to tailor typing lessons specific to your continuing progress. 

For _Kids_ and _School accounts_ :   
**NO** personally identifiable information is collected.   
For _all other users_ :   
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), unique identifiers (like a user name), and demographic information (like their sex, age, and income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Unique identifiers (such as user names) are collected for use as account numbers in our record system. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Users may opt out from email promotional offers at any time. 

This site contains links to other sites. Learn2Type.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**   
This site makes social media, chat rooms, forums, and/or message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**   
This site has resonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Kids under 18 years of age**   
In accordance with laws and safe practices, any account marked as a "kid" (i.e. age range selected during registration as under 18 years of age; or registration was performed at Kids.Learn2Type.com; or registration was a part of a Learn2Type for Schools enrollment) will have the following additional security safeguards: 

* **NO** personally identifiable information is collected; 
* Exercise content will be simpler and with educational content; 
* NO emails will be sent to kids accounts, unless email contact is initiated by the user (limited to answering support questions); 
* Banner ads displayed (if any) will be filtered; 
* Public areas will not be available to kids (Forum, Guestbook) to prevent contact with any third parties; 
* Additional security measures may be implemented at our sole discretion, if deemed necessary. 

**Third Party Advertising**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Third Party Cookies**   
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Contacting the Web Site**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us by postal mail at the address below, or [use the online feedback form](http://www.learn2type.com/Feedback): 

_Webmaster  
Learn2Type.com, Inc.   
PO Box 61569   
Staten Island, NY 10306-7569_   
privacyX@XLearn2Type.com 

|
